Okay, so yeah, so we're going to talk about fantasy
and about how to build a fantasy. I was going to say on cam, but
not just on cam. It's about building a fantasy.
You know, sometimes you'll be doing it in the moment and coming up with stuff in
the moment, but also it's really good to have things, to have a script already, to
have at least one script already that is like you can have it in front of you even
when you're on cam. And just to give you a bit of a prompt for what
to talk about or to give you different scenario or whatever.
I actually have a few now after years of doing it, I have quite a few.
So I know if someone comes to talk to me, I'll get a bit of a gauge to what kind
of thing they like, and then I can think about which one of my like scripts that
I can just roll off them, depends on what their character is.
So, yeah, so it's great to have scripts on cam for your confidence.
And obviously it can make calls a lot longer so what might have been just a quick
call can be a really long one if you can draw it out so much.
And it can build your like alter ego as well so you can build your character by having
so many different stories about what your character has done, whether you're like
acting, you know, being yourself on cam, or you're being a character or a bit of
both, which is what I do. Both really can have like made up stories about yourself
and then some of the things I say are true, and some of them are exaggerated.
And so it helps to kind of build your character.
And it's also fun. It's fun to do, and it's
a good thing to encourage people to come back and to become regulars because once
they get a bit of a taste of like fantasy and they know that you can give them something
a bit different, and you can really engage them in the story.
And, yeah, it gets them hooked so hopefully it gets you making some regulars as well.
And I think the more that you like get creative and the more effort you put in, like
we always say like any business, if you put effort into it, you're upskilling yourself,
you're going to earn more money, and it's building your creativity muscle as well
which is always a good thing I think. So, the components
of writing a script. So, I tried to, I tried to hone down on how do
I, how do I come up with or what are the good components, what are the good factors
that you need in writing a script and starting to write one.
So, you can write a script from scratch just when you're not on cam, just thinking
about all these things. But if you are on cam, it's a good place to start even before
you do it just thinking about your regulars or thinking about the people that come
into your room, because we're all different, aren't we, and we all attract different
types of guys. So if you're writing a script, you want it to be for the type of guy
that you attract anyway. And so, you know, I know that I attract a lot of older men
so that one of the, you know, I know that they're going to be my audience for starters.
And my profile is like, I'm a switch so you know I have like ones where I'm dominant
or ones where I'm submissive so I've got different types of things so I'm always
thinking about my clients first before I start thinking about any fantasies or scripts
that might come up with. And even when you're in the
chat, even just like looking at the person's username, you know, do they have anything
in their username that, you know, is telling you that they're dominant or submissive,
or they like some sort of role play. We all know, you know, there's lots of clues
there in the username. And, and not being afraid to ask people, you know, ask
them what they're into, ask them questions because questions are okay we don't have
to know everything, it's good to ask questions.
It's also good to remember that it's fantasy so I think so many girls,
especially when they're new, put off a lot of potential clients because they like
the people come in their room and they're like, oh I'm looking, I'm looking to meet
someone and they're like oh no don't do meets.
You know that's like, if you're not comfortable with going along with that whole
thing, then don't, but it's fantasy, remember that you're here
for a fantasy so of those guys that ask you to meet, probably 80%
of them are not really going to look to meet, you know.
As I say before I've had regulars, I've spoken to you for like five years and we
still talk about the meet we're going to have, like it's going to happen, you know.
We still talk as if it's real, but we both know it's not real, because we say the
same thing every time. So just remember that whatever you're talking about, only
talk about stuff that you're comfortable with, but it's not real, it's a fantasy.
So anything you're saying, don't worry, you're not going to have to do it, don't
worry about that. Can I ask you something?
This is where I've been going wrong, because I have been saying I don't do mates.
Yeah, and you know what, everyone says that, honestly, at the start, everyone's like,
oh my god, no, don't do meets. Yeah, I'm like, I'm really sorry I don't do meets,
and that's it, they're gone. Yeah, same with me, I'm still not quite comfortable
with talking about things like that. Yeah, and that's
fine as well, and that's fine as well. Even if you have a script in
your head, you don't even have to say, yes, I will, or no, I won't.
If you've got a script in your head, the easiest one to have is to say
to them, I'm not sure, I've never done a meet before, but I do have this fantasy,
and this is how I think it would go. So this is how I started, really, writing scripts
and thinking about these long role plays, because I kept getting asked all the time
about meetings, so I was like, okay. And then just, yeah, so I had my first
one that I'd say all the time, that I still say, is about, you
know, this, no, I've never done it, I'm not sure if I'll be comfortable, but I've
always fantasised about it. And this is how I think it would go.
So that's a good one, just to gauge it out and see if you feel comfortable with it
or not. Because you don't feel like you're committed to anything.
Yeah, that's what I'm going to do then now, because there's been quite a few that's
done that, especially overnight. Yeah, I just thought, oh,
you've got to, you know, they're going to just arrange to want to meet you and then
that's it. I mean, there are some who will want to, but there are escorts
on there, there's a whole massive section of escorts, so someone was just wanting
to look and get a meet, they could do it like that.
You know, they want to engage you, they want some fantasy, so, you know, you can
give them that fantasy. And you're behind the screen at the end of the day, you're
protected, you know, you can close that screen at any time.
Okay, so, so, remembering it's fantasy, and you've looked for any clues in
their name for like what sort of thing they might be into, but just an easy one is,
you know, oh yeah, I've always thought about meeting, I'm open to it, but not sure
if, you know, if I'm quite brave enough yet, but this is how I think it will go,
this is how I've imagined it in my head. So the next step would be the main character.
So the main character is you. So really giving them a feel for what the main character
is. So, for instance, doing that roleplay, that like little story,
that bit of fantasy about my meet, I would first think about, well,
I think about how they see me. So what do they see about me that makes them come
into my room, that makes them attracted to me.
So I know that, you know, my profile is all about being a professional, like I'm
a professional by day, and like by night I'm kinky.
So I know that they, they're attracted to me being that professional persona.
So I might say that I do a certain job, I work in an office, or I've got my own business,
just because I know that that's what's hooked them in already.
So giving them a little bit about your character and a little story, or a little
like intro into what you've been doing. So, yeah, I might say to them, Yeah,
I'm not, I'm not sure I've never done a meet before, I'm not sure if I'm ready yet,
but when I'm at work, you know, because I do this job and sometimes I'm sitting at
my desk and I'm thinking about meeting someone and what it might, what it might be
like. So I'm already setting the scene for them that I am this professional person
having this fantasy. And then think about
how you make them feel. So how do they want to feel?
Do they want you to be a really innocent person and they're like taking the reins,
or do they want to be like controlled, or do they want to be, what do they want?
It's usually quite, you're asking a few questions, engaging in the conversation,
you can usually get a little glimpse of what type of person they are, and what they
want from you. That sort of fantasy.
I've always fantasised about meeting, it's such a good one to start off with.
And you can even just sit down when you're not on cam and have a think about it.
So think about you as the main character, how you want to put yourself across, and
think about where would this meet be, what type of place would you like it.
So my thing that I always say is, I've always imagined that we'd be
going out for dinner. We'd be going out for drinks and we'd go out for dinner in
a hotel. And so I start my role play thing right at the start.
So I'm like, before I've even gone there, I tell them about, I've always thought
that I'd like to, you know, I can imagine myself getting ready.
Like I know where I'm going and I'm really nervous and I'm like putting my suspenders
on and some nice lingerie. And like I've got goosebumps thinking about what I'm going
to do. And so you're like setting the scene for them and you can drag it out so much
because you've not even got to the date bit yet.
And then, you know, this scenario. So whether it's in a hotel or whatever,
you know, might say we'll be having dinner.
And then, you know, I imagine it's like flirting and we can see other people looking
at us and we, you know, they don't know why we're here, but we know why we're here.
And like, you know, my legs sort of brushes against yours under the table.
So giving them like a sensory experience, you know, thinking about your senses,
what they can feel in that moment and really feeding them those little glimpses of
the sensory stuff. It's really good as well.
And my little thing that I always had, I don't know where this came from, because
you can find inspiration in everyday life in soaps, in just stuff that I watch
on Netflix. You can find inspiration for stuff that happens and put it into these
scenarios. So I don't know where this came from.
I think I read it or something once. Which is a good thing to do, actually.
There's loads of like erotica and stuff you can read online, which helps inspire
you. But I read about, I think it was in a book, there's this woman that was like,
she'd never met someone for sex before and she met him.
And then she, they had dinner and drinks and everything.
And he, it was just like, we'll have dinner and drinks and then if we get on, if
we like each other, then you can slide me an envelope across the table with like
a thousand pounds in or whatever. And then if I take it, then I'm yours for the evening.
Like, you know, if I don't take it, we're part company.
If I take it, then I'm yours for the evening and we know that, you know, we're in
it for the night. So I always used to use that fantasy and they liked that they love
those little details and the fact that you really thought about it because it's clear.
You know, you don't just come up with that sort of thing, do you?
It's clear. It makes it real for them because they really think, oh, she's been thinking
about this. She's had this fantasy. I can't tell you the amount of guys that I've
given that to. I can't tell you. Hundreds probably over the years.
So little things like that, little inspiration that you can get from life
can really make your story go that much, make it more real for them.
So thinking of a scenario, and that's just one example, that's just one example of
this is a fantasy I've had about meeting and this is how it might go.
But there are millions of examples, obviously.
I think I've talked about some before on other calls, but another one I often say
is that, oh, I've got this postman and he's really hot.
And I'm like, when he comes, I keep ordering things and he comes to deliver and I
get the feeling that he wants me to invite him in.
So I'm like, I've been going to the door and like less clothes or like with my shirt
open or something when I'm working and just like gauging his reaction.
And I'll say this to someone who's just come in my room who started talking to me
and I can gauge them on a bit of conversation.
And I'll just say, oh, yeah, just been to the door like this and then I'll tell them
this little story. And then you can go further with it and say, this
is how I imagine it's going to be. You know, this is what I imagine if I invite him
in, you know, this is what's going to happen.
And you can take that anyway, can't you? You can take that as in he's going to take
over, he's going to take control or I'm going to take control of him.
There's so many different ways that you can go with those stories.
So, yeah, thinking about the main character, which is you, thinking about
what they want from you. So what what what they enjoy, what's going to make them
feel good. Do they want to be in control?
Do they want you to be in control? And thinking about this sensory stuff, so
anything that you can describe which is sensory, like describing touch
or describing what they can see or what they can smell, even talking about your perfume
and things like that. And all of
this, like any of these scenarios, because there are like endless ones aren't there,
any of these scenarios, you are either talking
to them, I don't talk a lot when I'm on cam, hardly ever talk, I usually type, 90
% of the time I'm just typing. But while you're typing, you want to involve
your body and involve your body language in what you're doing while you're giving
them this fantasy. So if I get to a certain point in the story, which is a bit more
exciting, maybe I'm like, just taking the envelope from them in that fantasy, then
I might, like, just give them a little like, you know, deep breath or, because another
good thing is I leave my audio on. Even if I'm not talking, which I don't usually,
I'm usually typing, but I always leave my audio on because I like them to hear me
take a deep breath, have a little giggle.
And just those little things that they can hear in the background helps keep them
engaged as well because they really think you're into it.
Be good actress. So, so we've
thought about the main character, thought about what they want, thought about this
scenario, of which there are many I mean, I've given two examples but I
mean you could think about something that happens at work, maybe you're having an
affair with your boss. And, you know, maybe your, your friend, your flatmate's brother
has been looking at you while he comes over or, you know, something, you've
been travelling and something happened there.
There's so many little things where you can just get a snippet of a little naughty
thought and turn that into a whole fantasy.
And you thought about using your body and using your body language and a little sigh
here and there and whatever while you're saying it so that's keeping them really
engaged. And also, good to stop and check
in. So, rather than it you know this won't just be a total monologue, it won't just
be me talking the entire time, I'll be stopping here and there, maybe asking them
a little question so perhaps it's the fantasy about what, you know, meeting them
for the first time. And, you know, I'll say, yeah, you know, I've always
fantasised about getting ready about, you know, I'd be listening to this song and
thinking about what's going to happen and get goosebumps and I'll be getting dressed
and wearing some nice lingerie and I'll say, you know, what would you like me to
wear? What, what would, what would you enjoy knowing that I'm wearing under my clothes
for that first time? And so you're engaging them in the story and asking them questions,
and usually they're like, so keen to tell you what they want you to wear or
whatever. And I need, as you're going through the story, you
know, you can involve them again about, you know, how, how would you feel or what
would you think or what would you say or, you know, if you're imagining being on
a date with them like what would you order?
What would be your drinks order? So you're interested in them and you're involved
in them and making it seem a bit more real for them.
Yeah, so I think they're the main components really of building a fantasy.
So listening to what they want, thinking about you as the main character and remembering
it's fantasy. So you can be whoever you want.
You can be whoever you want, even from one call to the next.
You can be someone totally different. You know, you can be a nurse, you can be a
teacher, you can be a stepmom, anything you want to be from one call to the next
doesn't matter. And so, you know, you can really get into those characters, which
also makes it fun as well because like sometimes I'm a character which is like really
dominating and whatever and then other times I'm the total opposite.
But however you're feeling that day, it's quite fun to inhabit those characters isn't
it? So the character, the scenario and then
all the describing things and checking in with them and involving them.
And it's good to mention actually as well that, you know, you can talk about
real things. I mean, you know, whether or not you've got really sexy stories
that have happened. It doesn't happen to you, but it doesn't have to be imaginary.
You can use real things that have happened, or things that you've heard.
So you can approach it as in, this is a fantasy of mine.
You can say, this is something that happened to me, whether that's true or not.
Or you can do the meat thing, so there's a few different ways that you can do it.
It can be real or imagined, and it doesn't really matter.
A lot of the time it doesn't really matter to them, which one of those it is.
So I had a little think about some of the characters that you might be, but I
think that it's really important to find your own character, to
find your own thing that you enjoy. And you can find that by looking
back on some of our Zooms on the website, getting inspired by those.
Or just even going on Pornhub, or going on Erotica sites and
reading some stuff, and seeing what type of role plays people do, and whether you'd
find it fun to do those role plays. And you can have, there's loads
of innocent role plays, isn't there? Things that you're curious about.
So, I am really curious about having a threesome, or my boyfriend's suggesting
this to me and I'm not sure. Or even my boss in work is coming on to me a
bit, and I really want to go for it, but I'm not sure.
And there's more confident, experienced ones, so you could talk about sex parties
that you've been to, bondage places, or being tied
up or tying it to somebody else up. Or even things that don't seem overly
sexual sometimes to men are a massive turn on.
If you've controlled somebody, or manipulated them, then certain guys will find that
really hard. And they don't even have to be that sexual, those role plays.
And yeah, just the fantasy meet one, I think, when you're just starting out
to write fantasies and give guys a fantasy, fantasising about meeting them is
the best one, is the best way to start, I think.
Because it's so simple, you can talk about meeting them for a drink, you can put
little extras into it, you can talk about what you're wearing, how you're feeling,
and what's going to happen afterwards. And when it gets to the sex part, they usually
just take over. They usually just take over, because they so want to talk about that
part, that by the time you've fed them this whole long story, they're just like,
oh yeah, and then this, this, this and this.
So you don't even have to do the hard part, it's just leading all into it and then
letting them take the reins. Does anyone, does anyone want to give anything
that they've talked about or any advice they've got about fantasy?
I know Sammy, I don't know if you're there Sammy, Sammy does like a lot of
taboo stuff. Are you there Sammy? I'm here.
Hello. Not multitasking, but listening. Tell us
about, tell us about your taboo stuff Sammy, have you got any advice for people writing
like a dude? You'll be hard to hide girls.
Is it something that you could do? Can you give them like long drawn out sort of
scenarios? For the time, and also with Meet,
I get, so I've been camming for a while now, and I get asked every day
by the same people to meet them. And I think it's just a fantasy
because if they really wanted to meet someone, they just pick an escort.
They're not going to pay for a webcam and go, it's literally a fantasy in their head
as well so just go with it like, I can't, I honestly get asked all the time like
regularly for regular clients as well. So just go with it like, like you said, make
up a whole like fantasy and stuff. To be I mean it's something that you've got to
feel comfortable with. Because obviously I do a lot of like mummy play,
and like forced with daddy and that kind of stuff which is not everyone's cup of
tea. But if you, if you read like some literature
online and stuff like that you'll realise that it's something that's been written
about since the beginning of time, and it's always been a fantasy for men and women
over years and years and years. To me,
it doesn't really bother me because I know it's a fantasy and I'm okay with it.
I know a lot of girls will be like, oh my god, and wouldn't feel comfortable with
it, but it's okay. How do you get engaged for what they like, Sammi?
Do you have certain role plays that you just reel off your tongue because you
know them really well? Yeah, so like, you know, daddy getting into bed with you,
or if they like mummy play, it'll be like you say, oh come and get into bed
with me and suck on my boobies, and you use quite young language.
Do you know what I mean? Like, oh do you like that?
And I can feel under the covers that you're getting a bit excited.
Stroke mummy's face, like that kind of stuff.
Sometimes they'll, like, I always ask because some people like that, some people
to be would be a completely different thing.
Like, as soon as I say, oh I'd like to go to sex parties in real life, they're like,
oh amazing, and then I'll exaggerate on stuff that I've actually done.
So I'll say, you know, I've had like seven guys in each hole and
like massive big cocks and blah blah blah blah blah blah, when it wasn't quite like
that, you know, but I just exaggerate on that kind of thing.
And they, but if they don't like that, they'll tell you straight away, like they'll
say like, oh no, I like, if they like mummy play, they're not going to like you to
talk about seven big dicks fucking each hole of your body.
Do you know what I mean? So when they say, oh, I like all to do, I'm like, well,
no, it's specific, what do you like? I just ask.
And most of the time they're quite happy to tell you and then go from there.
But I always type because I find it so much easier than talking.
So if I type, it's like writing, I can make up this like massive story.
Whereas if I was talking, I'd be like, I wouldn't know what to say, which is so weird.
But my brain works in the way that I can type a lot quicker than it would like it
comes out better, if that makes sense. And it doesn't even have to be that quick
either, does it? Because that's what's keeping them on the call for ages, the fact
that you're typing. I never have my sound on so they know straight away that I'm
not going to talk to them. So they rarely get asked anymore because they can see
straight away that I've got no audio. So if they come into a group, they might ask
before they take me to private. Obviously, I'm not going to talk about them kind
of things in a group chat anyway. I use private to
talk about that kind of stuff. And a lot of guys as well, they don't want to talk
about like taboo subjects in group because they don't want people
to know what turns them on. Because it's taboo, from the point of it,
I suppose. And that's a good point. Sorry, go on, go on.
If anyone's thinking of like, you know, or like just looking into a little bit, like
look online. I can always post, there's a website, I can't think where it's called
now off the top of my head. But there's like loads and loads and loads of just literature
about taboo stories. And it just gives you so many ideas.
Like if you just read like a couple, it will then like
spark up and go, yeah, that's okay. I'll say this, that, whatever, whatever, whatever.
Like one guy just likes to tell me about how his wife's getting fucked by farm animals
down the road. Like she's blatantly not. No.
But he just types about it and like, he doesn't actually say what he's doing.
No, but he, yeah, and he's like, he comes in all the time.
He'll just keep saying like, oh, she'll ring me now.
I bet she's covered in cum, you know, you know what I mean?
And I go, oh, yeah, down at the farm. Like, I
know, it is, it's a bit like, to start off with, like, oh, my God.
Now I'm just like, where is she tonight? I
think, was it Literotica? There's a website called
Literotica. More stories as well. Yeah, that's the other one I see now.
Because the person that's going to be an adult baby yesterday.
Oh, yeah. I need to do a bit of research on this.
Because like, I put on, I went on, I did the.
I was at a Direct AM last night yesterday because I wanted to watch the Tinder swims
live, and I put on my tagline saying, let's talk taboo.
And that's the first person that's come in and said, well do you do this?
I'm like, do you finish this? I want to start getting into actually knowing more
about different things. Yeah, I get bored.
I'm just sat there and I'm like, yeah, yeah, I'll do this like another tier and I'm
like, sorry. And as soon as you know a little bit what you're
talking about, even if it's something that, you know, doesn't turn you on at all,
you know, if you know a little bit about it, they'll pick up on that, and they'll
love it. Like, you'll do well if you, if you like focus on one little thing that
you know, and then like read up about it and learn about it, they'll love that.
And that's so good that you can just get like a thing from someone like, do you do
this? And you can just look into it and just try it.
There's nothing stopping you from trying things, is there?
Yeah, we've been on Direct as soon as it comes to said, and I'm like, I'm not sure.
Search it straight away and I'm like, yeah, I'll do that.
Yeah, fair play to you for doing that, Kirsty.
I know that's, you know, I'm looking forward to it, to be honest with you.
First thing, I'm going up to Mum's house, so I'm going to be sat in my Mum's living
room doing it. Amazing. And
yeah, what you were saying about group and private, Sammy, as well, I think that's
worth mentioning that there's obviously role plays and stuff you can do in group
and ones that will only be for private. And I think like the little things that you
can say about people that you fancied or little naughty things that are not that
naughty, they're actually quite innocent, are really good things to say in group
or even in free, if you've got the attention to give to it in free.
You know, if you go in free chat and say, you know, the thing about the postman,
oh my God, like I nearly invited him in, I can't believe I nearly did that.
Or I just went to the door and like my shirt was open, I thought it was kind of on
purpose and now I feel like all this. Those kind of things will just have the guys
going crazy and it will be ping, ping, ping, everyone wants to talk to you about
it. So just the innocent ones that just give them a little snippet of something,
a really good in group, I think. I did what
I think it was you or Georgia recommended on the last call.
It was about saying that when you're in group, oh, who fancies come to come tonight?
It might be a three-year-old group, I can't remember now, and I was really dead one
night and I did that and straight away it was like ping, ping, ping, ping, like,
oh, they loved it. So worth trying. Yeah, yeah,
definitely. And I think you can also like out and out lie.
Like if somebody comes in and like their username is like BigDick47,
you can be like, yeah, just I've always been curious about being with someone with
a big dick. Like I've been watching some porn and I'm really into it.
I'm really nervous about it, but I really want to like, I really want to talk about
it. Just take what you can from their usernames and make it into your biggest fantasy.
And even if you think it's cringe what you're saying, because it's so obviously not
true. Mostly, most of the time they won't think like that because they're ruled by
their dicks. So they'll go along with it.
They'll enjoy it. How
are you feeling Hannah? We've had like a newbie in here talking about all these terrible
things. Yeah, I'm actually, I want a glamour model for 10 years.
Oh, amazing. I've done that, but obviously now I want to be at home or with kids
and what have you. But I do think I'm getting alright, but obviously there's a lot
to learn, isn't there? A lot to learn. So like, obviously, listening to you guys
and stuff, it obviously helps because we're their mates now and things like
that. I'll switch it up a bit. Yeah, yeah.
I can just try. I won't go to work tonight, but I feel like going on.
I'm going to go after this. I am too. I feel like trying it.
We've also got, because we're doing a new starter call now once a month, just
like a welcome call, just to go over a few bits.
So I think that's next week. You've probably had a message about it already, but
it might have been a while ago when you were set up Hannah.
I'm not sure. Going on when I set up, it were unreal.
I was there. Yeah, because obviously there's a group chat and getting to know everybody
and then figuring out this website. That works a few days
in itself. So yeah, I don't know if I've got that but I'll look out for it.
Yeah, there is so much and we do bombard you with so much information as well.
They've been amazing. You know, if I've put something on group chat or whatever,
then they've all helped. Yeah, the girls are amazing.
We're so lucky, so lucky to have these girls.
Yeah, so we'll just see. But yeah, I think I've done about five
hours, I think, and I'm up to 182 credits.
That's good. Fantastic. Yeah, it's really good.
I'm just hoping it's not just beginners luck.
No, it's fine and you don't have to know it.
That's the beauty of it. They love it when you're new and you don't have to know
everything straight away. You can just be yourself, can't you?
Yeah, but my laptop's not working either and the dog has chewed through the wire.
So I'm just about, well I was asking all the girls yesterday about a new laptop because
it's stressing me out. So I'm on my phone at minute.
So as soon as that comes and I can get that set up, it'll be 100 times easier.
Yeah, you've done that on your phone. Yeah, I've
only been on my phone. Put on your tagline, Hannah, you're
a glamour model. Yeah, and maybe you could like say some stories about, you
could make some stories about when you've been in a photo shoot and a photographer's
like, I don't know, touched you up or something like that.
They'd love that. Yeah. Just off the top of your head.
Right, right. If you put on your tagline, people will say to you like,
oh you're a glamour model. Oh,
I think we're losing you Sammy. Yeah, we're breaking up.
Yeah. But yeah, I think that's
such a good idea and even like being on a shoot with another girl and like being
a bit bi-curious and whatever. It would be a good one as well wouldn't it?
I've got loads of them. We've
lost you Sammy, sorry, that was cutting out then.
It always happens, doesn't it? Well
thank you for coming on ladies. I'm glad we went ahead with it in the end.
Yeah, thank you. And yeah, I hope you all make lots of money tonight
if you go on. I'm going to just take the jumper off now and transform.
I'm just in a little crop top and some shorts, I'm staying in that.
Yeah, go for comfort. Alright ladies, well it's lovely to see you.
And Hannah, I'll send you the thing for that new starters call.
And anyone who wants to just come on it if you want to come on it.
I think it's next Sunday. Is it on 16th? Yes, it is, yeah.
I remember because I've got a kids party on 16th as well and I remember.
Is it the same time? No. I don't think so, because I remember thinking,
oh what's happening on 16th? And then I thought, oh I've got a kids party at Softly.
Just a double life, I'm living it through, one life, cam girl.
But yeah, I'm sure it's totally about eight, nine.
Oh no, it's early, it's early isn't it? I think it might be in the afternoon, yeah.
I've got a kids party at my life by the bar, so I'm saying okay, I'll
be there. Alright then girls, well have a good night.
See you all very soon. See you soon, bye.